

MY CONTACT

Phone

09263880732

Email

yanneykool23@gmail.com

Address

Chesa St. Blk. 15, Lot 1, Phase C Porac IIB Brgy. Manibaug Paralaya Pampanga

Portfolio

https://yannie.info/

EXPERTISE

- With knowledge in CRM (SLA work)
- With knowledge Divi theme, elementor
- With knowledge of CSS,HTML,SASS,SEO
- With knowledge in MySql
- Basic Tech Support
- Coding (basic in ReactJS)

REFERENCES

Maureen Mondaga

Admin Tech

Phone

09699100398

DIANE DE GUZMAN WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

ABOUT MYSELF

Hello, I'm Diane. I'm an experienced comp. operator for 7 years, until I switched to web development. Apart from that, I'm also a competent software license agreement officer for a year.

As an IT professional, my area of expertise focuses on giving technical assistance to customers who are facing technical issues with the system software that my previous company provided, as well as monitoring 600+clients' databases.

Using WordPress and my working knowledge of React JS, I create websites and wanted to apply my web-building skills in practice.

EXPERIENCE

SLA OFFICER: 2022 - 2023 Servo IT Solutions

- Monitoring DATABASES of more than 600 clients (mostly hotels and restaurants that are partners of Servo. Also, scheduling replication (backups) and migration of clients' property.
- Monitoring client's subscriptions with CRM (Premium Support Services, Domain Names, Email Hosting).
- Company's first responder for technical assistance services
- Organizing and gathering confidential information from Servo's partners and clients.

Software Developer I: 2021 (Sept. to December) Servo IT Solutions

• Creating a react website for clients

Wordpress Developer: 2019 (Aug. to December) Sublime Web LLC

• creating a WordPress website using divi theme (builder) and elementor page builder, email support

Computer Operator I: 2013 - 2019 Department Of Tourism, Naia 1

- Encoding arrival and departure cards with a 1650 quota per day
- Sort Cards

EDUCATION

2012-2010 University Of Baguio

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Attended from 2010-2011 (undergrad.)

Associate of Computer Technology Major in Multimedia and Web Design

Attended from 2010-2012 (undergrad.)

2003-2007 Pines City National High School

Attended from 2003-2007

1996-2003 Coliling Elementary School

Attended from 1996-2003